After thousands of tips and a solid research work-
-Have I put together a top three list of the most extreme cases of spokenness.
You should meet the whole trio today.
We start at Södermalm in Stockholm, because here 19-year-old Elliot lives with mom and dad at home.
He has never ever contributed with work in the home-
-And even though he has a job, he really lives on his parents.
- He's your little prince.
Then we step in then.
- Elliot?
The baby, now you get to wake up.
Elliot Hörru, were you tired?
- My name is Elliot, I am 19 years old and turn 20 in a few months.
I would describe myself as very spoiled.
Gets serviced and curled at home.
Do nothing at home.
But I enjoy it.
- Never has anyone made such a tired and let go of this program.
- My dad prepares breakfast for me every day.
So it is served in the kitchen when I go up.
It feels like ... I'm almost a little sooty on you.
That you only get to paw here and as a 20-year-old get the whole breakfast served.
- Now you would like me.
-Gladly.
- And I understand that.
- What would have happened if this one was not here?
- Then we have a problem.
Then we have a very big problem.
First of all, it is ...
- Then we have a ...
- Yes, but then we have a huge problem.
- Elliot is always ... He always looks a little tricky.
You don't understand ... Is he spoiled for real?
Or is he just kidding a little?
- No, but he's spoiled.
- Do you know someone who is more spoiled than Elliot?
- Mmm ... no.
- In ... in ... no.
- Now I have soon eaten here.
- You have a lot left.
- Yes, though I'm done.
- Have you ever washed?
- No.
- But have you ever vacuumed?
- Have you never held a vacuum cleaner?
- Yes, I have held.
But I've never sucked.
- You understand where this is going.
- Now let's go and vacuum.
You need to do that when you live at home.
Electroluxus.
- What in ... no this I do not take responsibility for.
For real.
It is important that you are careful when sucking.
Hello.
- How much do you earn as a seller?
- A good month ... 30.
- What do you spend the money on?
- There will be a lot of exits.
- He has a good salary.
But really everything goes to night out.
- I don't want to hear that.
- I shouldn't have said that.
- No, that's not what we've agreed on.
Without him, he should save.
Your parents who pay.
Yes.
And if we look at this then.
Saving.
The mams and paps that save.
But is the question how it is on this others.
- Yes.
It's just tearing off the patch
- Oh!
- So there is SEK 30,000.
Your entire income sits on the rest.
Images.
But seriously, what do you think about this?
- When you put it up, it gets a little ...
- Hello!
- Warm welcome!
- Thanks!
- Hello, and welcome to Gävle!
- I called Mauri because my daughter Maja is spoiled.
- Hi Linda and Maja.
-Hello!
- What a happy hello!
- We are happy when you're here.
- Are you?
- Despite the very serious subject ...
- It's probably more you who have your opinions.
- But Linda, in what way is Maja spoiled then?
- She does not cook and does not wash.
Then she gets Swish of course.
Shoots do mom everywhere.
- I see her as my personal taxi.
- You see her as your personal taxi?
It is especially said by a girl who just said that she is not at all spoiled.
- When did you vacuum here last?
-Never.
- When did you last wash?
- I did on Christmas Eve.
Two glasses.
Carolina Gynning glass.
- She is spoiled, she does not spread her sandwiches herself.
- Doesn't their sandwiches burn yourself?
- No, she can't spread sandwiches.
So then Mom gets to spread sandwiches.
- It is such a detail that is difficult to just release, Maja.
That you cannot spread your own sandwich.
- It might be a little bad anyway when I think about it.
- This is almost historically then.
A seventeen -year -old who brings his first sandwich in life.
- Should I cut it?
- That's how you ... You know when you get bread from your mom in the morning she has cut it.
- Why don't you break first and then cut off?
Isn't that easier?
- You do as you wish.
- Yes, like this and burns, and then chop off.
It may be a little easier.
- No, do you not have to spread the other side?
- How to spread the other side?
- It's been wrong in the head.
I thought they did both.
So!
How nice!
- God, I feel almost awkward ...
- No, no it's quiet.
I'm used to everyone to ...
- Say you're spoiled?
- Yes.
So it's like ...
So do all my friends so ...
- Your friends also say that you are spoiled?
Everyone has the same opinion.
- But not yourself.
- No
- No argument bites?
- I don't think you can convince me.
- You are spoiled?
- You would almost want to have a debate between you.
A clear, with program manager.
So you can take your best arguments and then we will see who is right.
- Welcome to debatable debate.
Tonight it is about spoiled young people and curling parents.
- How spoiled is Maja?
- I think she is very spoken.
- What do you say Maja?
- I say I'm not.
- You're not spoiled?
- No.
Thanks for tonight.
We are back in a week and then it is about raspberry caves.
Could it be good sometime from time to time?
How many raspberry caves do you eat this week?
- Two three...
This afternoon was instead Maja who was allowed to push her mother down to the local gaming center.
- Then Linda, now me and Maja will go home and cook some food for you as you get when you come.
- God, so perfect.
Yes, I play yes a little.
At the same time, Maja had to stand at home and manage everyday chores.
And here we actually have to pause and just jointly try to take in how much detergent she thinks is needed to wash a single ladle.
- Oh...
God, what a luxurious.
Then it was time to cook minced meat sauce before Mom Linda's arrival.
- Maybe I should wait until it boils?
No, I'll put it down now.
I feel a little professional anyway.
- Do you?
- Yes!
- Yes, I can kind of.
I really try my best, I promise.
If you are to be honest?
- Then I'll be it ...
It wasn't good.
- How long have you been curled Maja in this way?
- She turns 18 in August, so it has become to curl her for 17 years.
To celebrate this curling anniversary, I took Maja and Linda to the local curling hall.
- Okay Linda, you have been curled your daughter for 17 years.
-Yes.
- You didn't understand why we were in ...
- No, I didn't.
Now I understood.
- Now you came in!
Are you ready?
- Yes!
- Good!
- And then you slip.
- Pretty!
You should simply curl, not your daughter but a stone today.
- Yes.
Yes!
- Okay, drive!
- So, that's good!
- It will put yours!
Because I'm going down to Åhus.
Now is the time to go to Åhus in Skåne where we find the number one list.
A 21-year-old who does not plug and who has not worked a single day throughout his life.
- But before you get to meet the main character himself, we will meet his best friend Hassan.
Is he the most spoiled person in Skåne?
- Yes, easy.
He is so spoiled.
In the days when we work as well, he is just home.
When we went to high school.
So, Jeppe could take a taxi to school and home from school.
- No!
- So, that's only half the study fraud.
- I have something to bite in there.
- Yes it really is.
- And here, my ladies and gentlemen, Jesper lives.
Behind this door.
Hello!
- My name is Jesper, I am 21 years old and I am extremely spoiled.
I love being spoiled.
I don't have to do anything, I don't have to work like everyone else.
So it's nice.
I have it easy in life.
- We can drive now.
We're going to start talking now.
- Also take the inner panel there.
- Which one do you mean?
- At the meter.
- At the meter?
No no.
- How spoiled would you say Jesper is?
- If I say this on a scale of 1 to 10 then you would say an 11.
- He's an 11.
- He's off the scale.
- What else has he paid for?
- Yes, for me to go and buy food for him.
Without working.
Sometime I think it will happen.
I have asked to God once.
- Have you?
Yes, and I said I want money in my account when I wake up.
- You are even a little spoiled when it comes to your relationship with God.
That you just, God give me money.
- Then I sat up and checked.
Closed.
- And what happened?
- Nothing.
- I do not know
- I have actually invited some who will enjoy a little to see you work.
Welcome!
- Axel, Hassan, Juan and Felix?
- It's all your friends.
It's all your friends who love you and are forced to stand out with your spokenness
Welcome!
- Thank you thank you.
- It comes more on the sides than on top.
Yes it is no longer, it just gets wider.
- Yes but how the hell should I do then?
- I love him as a person.
You want to pay tribute to him for making it.
It's a small task, but it's a big deal for him.
- That's what he's best at.
To break about their loved ones and dear family and friends.
- So, he can be spoiled, but it does not change how he is as a person.
- The situation was ...
It was degrading
- These are your first earned crowns in life.
Look at them!
- Are they genuine?
- Yes, yes, yes.
A beer round.
- Cheers for Jesper's first AW ever.
Before we make a point, I really want to thank all the guests who dared to show an honest side of themselves.
The charm troll Elliot with his bushy smile.
The wonderful curling duo Maja and Linda.
And then Jesper who really became happy and proud right into the reasons when I liked his local favorite pizzeria.
Of all the crimes you can be committed as a human being, a bit of a spoil is not the whole world.